NATHANIEL AKOBUNDU

UI/UX Designer & Developer



About Me

I am a product designer and a front-end developer, my artistic experience gives me the unique ability to apply design in all its forms to business processes. I have over 4 year of experience in user-centered design, user research, design thinking and strategy, with 2 years of experience in front-end development, my design tools include Figma, Illustrator, Invision, HTML, CSS, Bootstrap and ReactJS.

Experience

Product Designer | Solara Web

04/2022 - Present

- Collaborated with product managers on 5products from conceptualization to the final stages of development.
- Conducted competitor analysis and trend observations to better target user expectations and identify new product opportunities.
- Led monthly brainstorming sessions to facilitate new ideas for product improvement.
- Transformed my UI/UX design projects into a nice websites using HTML, CSS, Bootstrap and React.

Product Designer | Chelsea Group Itd 09/2019 - 02/2022

- Created wireframes, site maps, flow diagrams, and hi-fi interactive prototypes.
- Met with clients to sketching out all kinds of design for the project on paper or board.
- Collaborated with creative team members and developers to prepare mockups, concept art, storyboards, creative briefs and 3D models.

Contact Me

- +2349062172678
- +2347038988434
- udaice@yahoo.com
- 13 Adeoye Adeyemi, Maryland, Lagos.
- https://nath-akobundu.com

Social Profile

- https://linkedin.com/in/ nathanielakobundu-68a7b3118/
- **f** Akobundu Udochukwu
- @natario57

Other Info

Skills

- * Figma. *HTML. *CSS.
- *Bootstrap. *Photoshop.
- *Illustrator. *Invision. *Reactis
- *Microsoft Excel and

PowerPoint. *Pencil-on-

paper artist. *Good

command of English. *

Customer care relationship.

- *Research analyst.
- *Interpersonal skills.

UI/UX Designer | Lantora Itd

09/2018 - 08/2019

- Re-designed existing apps and websites to better adapt to new Mac, windows, android and iOS devices.
- Created User flows, wireframes, prototypes, and mockups.
- Presented UX design concepts to the project stakeholders for review and feedback.
- Translated user stories and business requirements into effective designs.

Education

| Abia State University BA International Relations and History | 2009 - 2013 |
|--|-------------|
| Google Coursera Certificate User Experience Design Process | 2018 - 2019 |
| Meta Coursera Certificate HTML and CSS In-depth | 2022 - 2022 |
| Angela Yu Udemy Certificate Complete Web Development Bootcamp | 2022 - 2023 |



Projects

Chelsea Group | Lepoll Website.

(12/2019 - 03/2020)

Designed and Developed the User Interface of the one pager website using ReactJS. https://lepoll.com/

2022 Limited | Workit Mobile App.

(01/2022 - 04/2022)

Designed a mobile app where you can hire the services of an artisan within your location.

Solara Group | Solara Group Website.

(08/2022 - 10/2022)

Redesigned the Solara Group website and it's subsidiary sites https://solaragroup.com/

Languages

English, Igbo.

Interest

Coding, Design, Art, Video games, Business, Football, Photography, Psychology, Drawing.

References

- SEUN SALIU.
 Software Engineer,
 Solara Group.
 seun@Salaweb.com.
 +447417487465.
- STANLEY CHIDOLUE.
 Project Manager,
 Chelsea Group Itd.
 chidoluechubueze@gmail.c
 om. +2348133913377.
- Dr. WAMBU CHIEMELA.
 Senior Lecturer,
 Abia State University.
 wambuc@gmail.com.
 +2348034071472.